https://www.area64assembly.org/privacy

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
Area 64 Assembly is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Area 64 Assembly site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Area 64 Assembly site, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of your Personal InformationArea 64 Assembly collects personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Area 64 Assembly also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Area 64 Assembly. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Area 64 Assembly for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Area 64 Assembly site.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Area 64 Assembly public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Area 64 Assembly does not read any of your private online communications.Area 64 Assembly encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Area 64 Assembly so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Area 64 Assembly is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Area 64 Assembly and Area 64 Assembly family of Web sites.Use of your Personal InformationArea 64 Assembly collects and uses your personal information to operate the Area 64 Assembly Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Area 64 Assembly also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Area 64 Assembly and its affiliates. Area 64 Assembly may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.Area 64 Assembly does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Area 64 Assembly may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Area 64 Assembly may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Area 64 Assembly, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Area 64 Assembly does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.Area 64 Assembly keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Area 64 Assembly, in order to determine what Area 64 Assembly services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Area 64 Assembly to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.Area 64 Assembly Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Area 64 Assembly or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Area 64 Assembly; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Area 64 Assembly, or the public.Use of CookiesThe Area 64 Assembly Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Area 64 Assembly pages, or register with Area 64 Assembly site or services, a cookie helps Area 64 Assembly to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Area 64 Assembly Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Area 64 Assembly features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Area 64 Assembly services or Web sites you visit.Security of your Personal InformationArea 64 Assembly secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Area 64 Assembly secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.Changes to this StatementArea 64 Assembly will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Area 64 Assembly encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Area 64 Assembly is protecting your information.Contact InformationArea 64 Assembly welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Area 64 Assembly has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Area 64 Assembly at admin@area64assembly.org. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Quick Links:
A.A. World Service
A.A. Grapevine
ICYPAA
TCYPAA
Our Three Legacies are Recovery, Unity and Service
Menu
A.A. World Service
A.A. Grapevine
ICYPAA
TCYPAA
Our Three Legacies are Recovery, Unity and Service
Legal Notice
This website is not endorsed or approved by the General Services Office of Alcoholics Anonymous. The contents of this site are the responsibility of Area 64’s Public Information & Website committees. Alcoholics Anonymous, AA, and The Big Book are registered trademarks of Alcoholics Anonymous World Services, Inc.
Copyright 2019 Area 64 Assembly
Privacy Statement | Terms Of Use
don't worrybe happy.WE HAVE A NEW AREA 64 WEBSITE.
Use the forgot password feature on the login page to reset your password. If you have any problems please use the contact form in the footer of the home page and select Technical Support.
